worxware.com 2016-10-27

# Worx International Inc. - WorxWare.com

### Privacy Policy

(Updated on July 04 2008)

Worx International Inc. respects and protects your privacy. While browsing our website pages you do not need to provide any information about yourself. However, there may be times we need information to provide services that you request, and this privacy statement explains data collection and use in those situations.

We will request your personal information only when we need to personally identify you or to contact you. This is only required when you request information, quotation or a response to your email. Personal information collected by Worx International Inc. is limited to e-mail address, basic contact information and your comments, but may also include other data when needed to provide a service you requested.

Collected information may be stored and processed in Canada, United States or other country where Worx International Inc.'s main office, subsidiaries or affiliates maintain facilities. We use a variety of technologies and operations security in order to protect your personal information from disclosure, loss, misuse, alteration, or destruction. Only authorized personnel of Worx International Inc. has access to personal information and are required to treat this information as confidential.

We may disclose your personal information if:

  1. Required to do so by the laws, rules, and regulations of any nation, state, or other applicable jurisdiction.
  2. You consent to such disclosure.
  3. We need to protect and defend the rights or property of Worx International Inc. and related websites.

While providing links to other websites, we do not guarantee the same and can not be responsible for the information collection and privacy practices of such third-party websites, which may differ from our site's policies. 

The family of Worx International Inc. sites was not intentionally designed or directed at children 15 years old or younger. Being especially committed to protect children's privacy in on-line environment, we do not knowingly collect or maintain personal information from children.

By using this website, you consent to collection, use and storage of your personal information by us in the manner described in this privacy statement and elsewhere on the website. We reserve the right to update this privacy statement. The "Updated on" date at the top of the privacy statement indicates the date of the document's last revision.
